Just ten more minutes.
Maybe five. Wake up! Now!
Sugu?
Would you get up already?
It's 5.30.
Even though you're a lost
child to Vecta and a guest,
you're still expected to get up on time.
Okay.
So let's
do
this.
I'm living in the darkness.
I'm feeling it.
Yourself.
I'm having a love song. I'm watching it.
I'm seeing it on the day.
Shiny summer diamond I'm feeling it.
Let's go to the beginning of the world.
Let's dive into the rocket's orbit!
Let's dive into the light.
Let's dive into the sky?
What time do you think?
I'm here to come.
I have to think about taking place.
Let's go to the end of the world.
On the end of the world.
There's a lot I don't understand about
this place, but I know I'm gonna need.
Eugeo's help to get to Senator.
Thing is, I have to get him
out of his Calling first.
And to do that, we'll have
to chop this tree down.
What was that? Huh? Oh, nothing.
We're all done with the morning's quota.
It's time for lunch.
I'm starving.
You know what I wish?
I wish you could have
tasted the pies Alice made.
The crust was so flaky and
there was so much filling.
Having it with some
fresh milk was the best.
There's nothing in the world
that tasted better than that.
Was that Alice's calling? A baker?
No, not even.
Back in those days, she was studying
the sacred arts at the church.
She was the greatest prodigy
this village ever had.
She could cast all kinds of
spells by the time she was ten.
Wow.
What's up with the girl
living at the church?
You know, Selka?
Oh, she's Alice's little sister.
After Alice was taken away,
Selka moved to the church to become
a nun and study the sacred arts.
There's a bunch of kids there, too.
Are they there for the same reason as her?
They lost their parents to the plague
that hit the village three years ago.
The church is the only place that
had room for them. Poor kids.
It's like we're cursed.
All these strange things
have been happening lately.
Like people being attacked and
kidnapped down the main road.
The villagers say goblins
are the ones doing it.
There's goblins here?
I have a feeling all
that talk's just rumors.
If it were true, an Integrity Knight should
have come by now to put a stop to them.
They'd have been here in a flash.
Like when Alice touched the
ground in the Dark Territory.
That was nothing compared to goblins.
No, it's not. Either way,
there have been a lot of deaths over the
past two or three years, more than usual.
Can't you revive them?
You know, like with
one of the sacred arts?
Well, I don't know about that,
but I remember Alice saying
there was a high-level
sacred art that could stop
a life from decreasing.
That'd be a good one to know, I guess.
It would.
Alice said she found a passage about that
spell in one of the old
books in the church.
But the problem is, only the high
priest at the Axiom Church can use it.
Axiom Church?
It's in Senator.
They wrote the Taboo Index.
But, like, do you have to be a
high priest to use the spell?
Maybe someone like you
or me could learn it.
No, it's not for regular folk like us.
The arts get their strength
from the sacred power
that Solus and Terraria
saturate the air and land with.
The more elaborate the art,
the more sacred power it takes.
It would take more power
than this forest has,
and no one from here to
Zakaria could wield it.
That's too bad I wonder
if there's a sacred
art that could help us
to chop this thing down.
That would make things easier there's
gotta be something better than this.
Oh hey Yugio is there anything
tougher than this in your village?
No I'm afraid not the only thing.
Stronger than the dragon
bone axe would be an
integrity night on second
thought maybe there is.
Wait here for me.
I'll be back in a bit.
Huh?
Whoa, you okay?
Mind if I open it?
Okay.
Just be careful.
If it falls on your foot, it'll
leave you with more than a scratch.
No way.
It's the blue rose sword
from the fairy tale.
What fairy tale?
It goes like this.
300 years ago, Bercouli the
swordsman went to the End Mountains.
He entered the lair of the white dragon,
our protector, and found that sword.
It's just a silly story.
That is, it was, until some kids
decided to find out if it was true.
I mentioned it yesterday.
Remember?
About how Alice and I
went to the End Mountains?
I found that sword in the dragon's lair.
I couldn't even lift it by
myself back then. Really?
What'd the dragon have to say about
you guys breaking into its home?
There was nothing left
of it except some bones.
We took the wrong tunnel, and then
Alice crossed into the Dark Territory.
And then she was taken away.
I couldn't do anything for
her except stand there.
I wanted to save her, but my
arms and legs were frozen.
I'm sorry.
Back to the sword.
I left it there that
day and never forgot it.
So two summers ago, I went back.
Every day of rest, I'd go drag it.
It took three months to get it back here.
It took you three whole months to do it?
Why'd you even bother?
I guess I was hoping one day I'd
have the strength to swing it.
I'm still not strong enough to.
Do you think you are?
I'm down to try.
I'm a swordsman, after all.
Looks like it's too heavy for you, too.
It's not made of steel, or is it?
No, I don't think so.
And it's not silver or dragon bone either.
I think it might be a
divine object. Of what?
It's something that was either made with
the help of the gods
or was created by them.
We call things like that divine objects.
That makes sense.
Hey, Eugeo, could you, like, check
how much life the Giga Cedar has now?
Don't tell me.
Let me guess.
You're going to try
striking it with the sword.
You're damn straight, I am.
Unless the Taboo Index forbids it.
But I bet it doesn't, does it?
No, it doesn't. It's funny.
All this seems so familiar.
Right now, it's at 232,315.
Cool.
Remember that.
Did you hurt yourself?
No, I'm okay.
I told you before, that tree is tough.
No way.
You actually cut into it.
And deep, too. Go on.
See where its life's at now.
Oh, right.
2-30-2-3-14.
You're kidding.
It only went down one point?
Your hit landed in the wrong spot.
I bet it would have decreased
its life a lot more if
you got it in the center of
the cut instead of the bark
Looks like your intuition was right.
The sword is more effective
than the axe Even so
we'd have to master using
it to get any results.
I can't hit it straight,
but I bet you could I can barely
hold the sword let alone swing it.
It's all about technique and
I can help you with that.
Okay I'll give it a shot.
It's... so heavy.
First thing, find your balance.
And when you swing, swing with your body.
With swords, it's more about
momentum, not just arm strength.
Mm-hmm.
Whoa!
Hey, you all right?
I think I lost some life on that one.
Oh, well, it was a good try.
If durability's life, I lost
some when I took a swing.
Hmm, it says my object
control authority's at 38.
I guess that's my parameter.
The sword is higher.
That's what I'm talking about.
At this rate, I'll never get to Senator.
I need Eugeo's help, but he
won't bail on his calling.
If it wasn't for that taboo index,
he could do whatever he wants.
He said the Axiom Church came up with it.
Wonder what the deal is with them.
If I'm right and these people are AI
Fluctlights in a simulated civilization,
there's no way the system
would let them break a rule.
Hang on.
Yu-Gi-Oh said Alice broke
the Taboo Index when
she accidentally crossed
into the Dark Territory.
But she was there by choice.
She went against the system.
So is she not an AI? Hello?
Is someone in there?
Yeah, there is.
I'm almost done.
Oh, um, no.
You can take your time.
I was just checking.
Sorry to bother you.
Good night.
Uh, Selka!
I wanted to ask you something.
So, what was it you wanted to ask me?
Yeah.
Um, it's about your older sister.
I heard about her, you
know, from Yu-Gi-Oh.
And, like, he told me her name was Alice.
He did, did he?
What else did he tell you
besides her name was Alice?
Oh, um, he said she was studying
the sacred arts here at the church.
And how six years ago an
Integrity Knight took her.
I got the feeling he's
really worried about her.
I didn't know.
I thought he forgot about her.
This explains a lot about him, though.
She's the reason Eugeo's so sad.
I didn't get that.
He seems fine. He's not.
You had to have noticed it.
How quiet and gloomy he is.
Oh, yeah.
When my sister was here,
every time I saw him, he
had a smile on his face.
I don't remember ever seeing
him without one back then.
But not anymore.
He spends his days of rest alone,
and the only time I see him
is when he goes to the forest.
Selka, you really like him, don't you?
Ah!
I didn't say that! Oh my gosh!
Everyone compares me to Alice.
No one says it, but I know.
When my parents see me,
I remind them of her.
And I can't stand it anymore.
That's probably why Eugeo avoids me.
When he sees me, he thinks of her
and I can tell it makes him sad.
But there's nothing I can do.
It's not my fault she's gone.
I'm sorry, I'm acting like a baby.
No, not at all.
It's good to cry.
It's better than holding it in.
Yes, you're right.
In fact, I feel much better already.
Crying in front of others
is not something I do.
Really?
You're tougher than I am.
I can't tell you how many times
I've cried in front of people.
Hold on.
Is your memory back? No!
It just feels that way is all.
Anyway, back to you.
It doesn't matter what anyone thinks.
You're you, not your sister.
You can only live your
life, not someone else's.
Yes, you're right.
I should get going.
Say, did Eugeo happen to tell you why
the Integrity Knight took my sister away?
Um, yeah, he did.
My parents wouldn't tell me.
And Eugeo wouldn't tell me either.
Maybe you could tell me why? Yeah, sure.
She went to the End Mountains, then touched
the ground on the Dark Territory side.
I see.
The End Mountains, huh?
Tomorrow's our day of rest.
Still, be on time.
I won't be coming to wake you up anymore.
Okay, I'll keep that in mind.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
By chance.
Have you seen Selka today? No.
I just woke up, actually.
So I see.
Well, I have not seen her all morning.
She missed prayers, and
she is not in her room.
I am worried.
She would never leave
without telling me first.
I'm sure she's around.
I hope so.
If you see her, please
let me know. Yes, ma 'am.
Yujiu! Hey, Kirito.
Have you seen Selka anywhere?
I haven't. Why?
Sister Azalea's been looking for her.
She says she left without telling her.
That's strange.
Well, I'm trying to find her.
Do you know where she could have gone?
No, she and I haven't spoken in ages.
Do you think something
might have upset her?
I see.
The End Mountains, huh?
Oh, man.
Last night, I told her
what happened to Alice.
At least everything you
told me that happened.
She wouldn't go to the End
Mountains on her own, would she?
That's exactly where she went!
We have to bring her back now!
What's wrong?
It's been stepped on.
It's lost a bit of life.
Someone's been by here, and
it wasn't that long ago.
Then we're on the right track.
That's gotta be Selka.
Yeah.
Well, this is it.
No way.
It really is the end.
When I first came here,
I thought the same thing.
And the dark territory's
down that way, huh? Yeah.
Are you ready?
Yeah, I think. I guess.
System call.
Generate luminous elements.
Adhere.
Yu-Gi-Oh, what'd you do?
It's a sacred art.
An easy one that anybody can do.
But, like, you said system.
Do you even know what that means?
Nothing.
It's just a word.
Well, a command.
It's to call on the gods.
As long as you have enough skill, you'll
be blessed with the art you summon.
He thinks he's casting a magic spell.
Come on, let's go. Right.
Maybe she didn't come in here.
I mean, there's no sign of her.
This is as good a sign as any.
It could be her, I guess.
Hey, Yujiya. What is it?
If she crosses into the Dark Territory,
does an Integrity Knight
come and take her right away?
No, not until the next day.
He'll fly to the village and arrest
her there, just like six years ago.
Then, even if we're too late, we still
have a chance to keep him from getting her.
But that would be interfering. We can't.
Of course we can.
Look, even if she does
break the taboo index,
all we have to do is keep
her away from the village.
The Integrity Knight can't
arrest her if he can't find her.
That's insane.
We can't hide forever.
And I have my calling.
But I don't, so I can take her away.
If I didn't say anything,
she wouldn't be in this mess.
This is all on me.
No, it's not.
Sugou!
That way!
Take cover!
Crap. Goblins.
Sugou!
What are you doing?
Looky, looky.
Two more white Eum Brassy Brats
just a-wandering around. Yummy!
Let's tie him to the other one!
Silence!
They're male youths.
We take them back, no one buy them.
Worthless.
Kill them and make them meat instead.
Eugeo!
Eugeo?
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Oh...
If you're bright, I'll
see the sun in the sky.
I'll see the sun in the morning.
For my tears, when I'm out of my tears,
I'm not a pain.
It's not your eyes.
If you're my body, I'm feeling it.
It's a pain that I've felt, I'll
be able to give you some pain.
Next time, Departure.